CHELSEA OKTAVIANY

087788636865 | chelseaoktaviany97@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/chelseaoktaviany

PROFILE SUMMARY

Recent university graduate Informatics major with a specialization in Web development. Have been working mostly with web development using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, and basic Laravel for 2 years of experience through projects. Skilled in team collaboration, analyzing, and communication. Looking for jobs that provide opportunities for further development.

EXPERIENCE

COVID-19 Response Acceleration Task Force, Jakarta

Back-End Developer Intern (June, 2020 - September, 2020)

- Experienced as Back End Developer in building task-force website with HTML, CSS and PHP
- Knowledge on database relationship between customer, COVID history, and location
- Experienced in Data Entry and Engineering with MySQL

CMS Puskesmas | Web Development Project

Web Developer (February, 2022 - March, 2022)

- A project is to build a Content Management System web application for doctors, patients, and admins including login, register session, dashboard, CRUD patient, medicines, schedules, etc.
- Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and Native PHP to build the CMS website
- Using MySQL to create a database called cms_puskesmas

Personal Website | Web Development Project

Web Developer (May, 2022 - Present)

- A project is to build a web application for my personal includes about me, my skills, my projects, and contact
- Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript, Bootstrap 5 as CSS framework to build the frontend website
- Using Netlify web deployment to deploy the personal website

EDUCATION

Cahaya Sakti Vocational High School (July 2014 - May 2017)

Vocational High School, Multimedia

Kalbis Institute (September 2017 - December 2021)

Bachelor of Computer Science, Informatics

GPA: 3.71 / 4.00

• Awards: Doodle Art - 3rd Place in Waffle 2017 Event Kalbis Institute

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, Laravel, ReactJS, MySQL, NPM, Yarn
- Soft Skills: Debugging, Problem-Solving, Analytical, Teamwork, Communication skills
- Tools: Git, Heroku, Visual Studio Code (IDE tool)
- Languages: Indonesian (Native), and English (Passive)
- Certifications: HTML Essential Training